Guide to the William A. Speck Collection of Prints
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Oversize, 30.02; (21 boxes) + 204 broadside folders
  - BOXES: PORTRAITS
    - "F"
      - Freundstein, Henriette W von (Box 23, Folder +)
      - Friedrich II, der Grosse, King of Prussia, 1712-1786 (Box 23, Folder +)
      - Friedrich August, duke of Braunschweig-Oels and Bernstadt, 1740-1805 (Box 23, Folder +)
      - Fromann, Friedrich Johannes, 1797-1886 (Box 23, Folder +)
    - "G"
      - Gellert, Christian Fuerchtegott, 1715-1769 (Box 23, Folder +)
      - Genast, Caroline Christine (Böhler), 1800-1860 (Box 23, Folder +)
      - Gersdorf, Ernst Christian August von, 1781-1852 (Box 23, Folder +)
      - Gessner, Salomon, 1730-1788 (Box 23, Folder +)
      - Gleim, Johann Wilhelm Ludwig, 1717-1803 (Box 23, Folder +)
      - Goethe, Johann Kaspar, 1710-1782 (Box 23, Folder +)
      - Gottsched, Johann Christoph, 1700-1766 (Box 23, Folder +)
      - Graff, Anton, 1736-1813 (Box 23, Folder +)
      - Griesbach, Johann Jacob, 1745-1812 (Box 23, Folder +)
      - Grimm, Herman Friedrich, 1828-1901 (Box 23, Folder +)
      - Grimm, Jakob Ludwig Karl, 1785-1863 (Box 23, Folder +)
      - Grimm, Wilhelm Karl, 1786-1859 (Box 23, Folder +)
      - Goethe
        Busts
        - Miscellaneous (Box 24, Folder ++)
        - David (Box 24, Folder +)
        - Klauer (Box 24, Folder +)
        - Rauch (Box 24, Folder +)
        - Trippel (Box 24, Folder +)
        - Trippel - Schaufuss - Brinckmann (Box 24, Folder +)
        - Caricatures
          - Beerbohm (Box 24, Folder +)
        - Monuments
          - Miscellaneous (Box 24, Folder +)
          - Berlin Tiergarten (Box 24, Folder +)
          - Frankfurt A.M. (Box 24, Folder ++)
          - Weimar (Box 24, Folder +)
        - Portraits
          - Original drawing for Buenos Aires newspaper "La diaria Voz de Critica" (Box 24, Folder +)
          - Bager (Box 24, Folder +)
          - Dawe (Box 24, Folder ++)
          - David (Box 24, Folder +)
          - Jagemann (Box 24, Folder +)
          - Kolbe (Box 24, Folder +)
          - Kügelgen (Box 24, Folder ++)
          - Kraus (Box 25, Folder ++)
          - Lalauze (Box 25, Folder +)
          - Lips (Box 25, Folder +)
          - May (Box 25, Folder +)
          - Pecht (Box 25, Folder +)
          - Rauch (Box 25, Folder +)
          - Rollett (Box 25, Folder +)
          - Schmoll (Box 25, Folder +)
          - Sebbers (Box 25, Folder +)
          - Stieler (Box 25, Folder +)
          - Stieler - Thackeray (Box 25, Folder +)
        - Reliefs
          - Melchior (Box 25, Folder +)
        - Statuettes
          - Rauch (Box 25, Folder +)
        - Goethe im Bild
          - Fleischer, Fritz, Mehr Licht! (Box 25, Folder +)
    - "H"
      - Haizinger, Frau Amalie Morstadt, 1800-1884 (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Harrach, Karl Borromaus, Graf von (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Hauptmann, Gerhart (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Heine, Heinrich, 1797-1856 (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Herder, Johann Gottfried von, 1744-1803 (Box 25, Folder ++)
      - Hess, Freiherr von (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Hess, Johann Jakob, 1741-1828 (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Heygendorf, Frau Henriette Caroline Friedrike Jagemann von (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Heyse, Paul Johann Ludwig von, 1830-1914 (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Hugo, Gustav, 1764-1844 (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Humboldt, Alexander, Freiherr von, 1769-1859 (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Humboldt, Wilhelm, Freiherr von, 1767-1835 (Box 25, Folder ++)
    - "I"
      - Iffland, August Wilhelm, 1759-1814 (Box 25, Folder +)
    - "J"
      - Jung-Stilling, Johann Heinrich, 1740-1817 (Box 25, Folder +)
    - "K"
      - Kant, Immanuel, 1724-1804 (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Karl, Archduke of Austria, 1771-1847 (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Karl Alexander, grand duke of Saxe-Weimar-Eisenach (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Karl August, duke of Saxe-Weimar-Eisenach, 1757-1828 (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Karl Friedrich, grand duke of Saxe-Weimar-Eisenach, 1783-1853 (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Kauffmann, Angelica, 1741-1807 (Box 25, Folder ++)
      - Kauffmann, Christoph, 1753-1793 (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Kellermann, François Christophe (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Kestner, August, 1777-1853 (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Kestner, Charles, 1776-1846 (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Kestner, Frau Charlotte Buff (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Kestner, Hans Ernst Hermann, 1786-1871 (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Kleist, Heinrich von, 1777-1811 (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Klinger, Friedrich Maximilian von, 1752-1831 (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Klopstock, Friedrich Gottlieb (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Koch, Frau Christiane Henriette Merleck (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Koch, Heinrich Gottfried, 1703-1775 (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Kotzebue, August Friedrich Ferdinand von, 1761-1819 (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Krüger, Karl Wilhelm, 1791-1841 (Box 25, Folder +)
      - Kügelgen, Gerhard von, 1772-1820 (Box 25, Folder +)
    - "L"
      - Lamartine?, Alphonse Marie Louise de, 1790-1869 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Langhans, Madame (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Lavater, Johann Caspar, 1741-1801 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Leisring, Christian August Joachim (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Lessing, Gotthold Ephraim, 1729-1781 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Lips, Johann Heinrich, 1758-1817 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Loder, Justus Christian von (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Loewe, Karl, 1796-1869 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Ludwig I, King of Bavaria (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Lucchesini, Girolamo, Marchese, 1751-1825 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Lucinde, die schöne Strassbürgerin (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Ludwig, Christian Gottlieb, 1709-1773 (Box 26, Folder +)
    - "M"
      - Maria Ludovica Beatrix Antonie Josephine, empress consort of Franz I, emperor of Austria, 1787-1816 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Mariia Pavlovna, grand duchess of Saxe-Weimar-Eisenach, 1786-1859 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Mara, Frau Gertrud Elisabeth Schmeling, 1749-1833 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Mara Luise Augusta Katharina, empress consort of Wilhelm I, German emperor, 1811-1890 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Mendelsohn-Bartholdy, Felix i.e. Jacob Ludwig Felix, 1809-1847 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Meyer, Hans Heinrich, 1760-1832 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Monti, Vincenzo, 1754-1827 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Moors, Johann Isaak, 1707-1777 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Morus, Samuel Friedrich Nathanael, 1736-1792 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Muller, Johann Gotthard, 1747-1830 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Mullner, Amadeus Gottfried Adolf (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Musaus, Johann Karl August, 1735-1787 (Box 26, Folder +)
    - "N"
      - Napoléon I, emperor of the French, 1729-1821 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Nees von Esenback, Christian Gottfried Daniel, 1776-1858 (Box 26, Folder +)
    - "O"
      - Oeser, Adam Friedrich, 1717-1799 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Overbeck, Friedrich, 1789-1869 (Box 26, Folder ++)
    - "P"
      - Passavant, Jakob Ludwig, 1751-1827 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Pfenninger, Heinrich, 1749-1815 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Pfenninger, Johann Konrad, 1765-1825 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Plitt, Johann Jokob, 1727-1773 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Preller, Friedrich Johann Christian Ernst, 1804-1878 (Box 26, Folder +)
    - "R"
      - Racknitz, Joseph Friedrich, Freiherr von, 1744-1818 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Rauch, Christian Daniel, 1777-1859 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Reiffenstein, Johann Friedrich, 1719-1793 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Reinhard, Franz Volkmar, 1753-1812 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Richter, August Gottlieb, 1742-1812 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Richter, Johann Thomas, 1728-1773 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Richter, Ludwig, 1803-1884 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Ridel, Johann Cornelius Rudolf, 1759-1821 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Röhr, Johann Gottfried, 1764-1850 (Box 26, Folder +)
    - "S"
      - Schadow, Johann Gottfried, 1764-1850 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Scheffauer, Philipp Jacob, 1756-1808 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Scheffer, Ary, 1795-1858 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Schelling, Friedrich Wilhelm Joseph von, 1775-1854 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Schiller Monuments (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Schiller Busts (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Schiller, Johann Christoph Friedrich von, 1759-1805 (Box 26, Folder ++)
      - Schinkel, Karl Friedrich, 1781-1841 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Schmalz, Theodor Anton Heinrich, 1760-1831 (Box 26, Folder +)
      - Schreiber, Carl Friedrick (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Schröder, Friedrich Ludwig, 1744-1816 (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Schubert, Franz Peter, 1797-1828 (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Schuppach, Frau Marie Flückigger, 1735- (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Schüppach, Michael, 1707-1781 (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Sontag, Henriette, 1806-1854 (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Speilmann, Jacob Reinbold, 1722-1783 (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Starck, Johann Jakob, 1730-1796 (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Steffens, Henrich (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Stein, Charlotte von, 1742-1827 and Stein family (Box 27, Folder +)
    - "T"
      - Talleyrand (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Talma, François Joseph, 1763-1826 (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Tasso (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Taylor, Bayard, 1825-1878 (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Textor (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Thorvaldsen, Bertel, 1770-1844 (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Thummel, Moritz August von, 1738-1817 (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Tieck, Johann Ludwig, 1773-1853 (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Tiedge, Christoph August, 1752-1841 (Box 27, Folder ++)
      - Tischbein, Johann Heinrich, 1722-1789 (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Türckheim, Anna Elisabeth von, 1758-1817 (Box 27, Folder +)
    - "U"
      - Unzelmann, Carl Wilhelm Ferdinand, 1753-1832 (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Uz, Johann Peter (Box 27, Folder +)
    - "V"
      - Vogelstein, Vogel von (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Varnhagen von Ense, Karl Aug. L. P. (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Varnhagen von Ense, Rahel (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Vogel, Carl, 1798-1864 (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Volpato, Giovanni (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Voss, Marie Christine Ernestine (Box 27, Folder +)
    - "W"
      - Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883 (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Walch, Frau Christiane Friedrike Wilhelmime Herzlieb (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Weber, Bernhard Anselm, 1764-1821 (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Weyland, Philipp Christian, 1765-1843 (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Wieland, Christoph Martin, 1733-1813 (Box 27, Folder ++)
      - Wilheim, Herzog von Nassau, 1792-1839 (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Winkler, Gottfried, 1700-1771 (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Wolff, Pius Alexander, 1782-1828 (Box 27, Folder +)
    - "Z"
      - Zelter, Karl Friedrich, 1758-1832 (Box 27, Folder +)
      - Zimmermann, Johann Georg, Ritter von (Box 27, Folder +)
    - Unidentified
      - Unidentified (Box 27, Folder +)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Goethe, Johann Wolfgang von. His Drawings
        - Italy (Box 28, Folder +)
        - Switzerland (Box 28, Folder +)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder +)
      - Lavater - Miscellaneous silhouettes and drawings from the Physiognomische Fragments (Box 28, Folder +)
      - Man, in the Nude by Nat Smolin (Box 28, Folder +)
      - Schadow - Works (Box 28, Folder +)
    - Miscellaneous - Actors
      - Faust (Box 28, Folder +)
      - Brückner, as Götz (Box 28, Folder +)
      - Bethmann (Box 28, Folder +)
      - Actors in various parts except Faust (Box 28, Folder +)
    - Lavater
      - Prints and portraits from his Physiognomische Fragmente (Box 28, Folder +)
      - Empty box (Box 29)
  - BOXES: VIEWS
    - Czechoslovakia
      - Karlsbad (Box 30, Folder +)
    - France
      - Champagne (Box 30, Folder +)
      - Savoie (Box 30, Folder +)
      - Verdun (Box 30, Folder +)
    - Germany
      - Alexandersbad (Box 30, Folder +)
      - Allstedt (Box 30, Folder +)
      - Berlin (Box 30, Folder +)
      - Bingen (Box 30, Folder +)
      - Braunau (Box 30, Folder +)
      - Breslau (Box 30, Folder +)
      - Eisenach (Box 30, Folder +)
      - Eisenach - Wilhelmsthal (Box 30, Folder +)
      - Elfeld (Box 30, Folder +)
      - Frankfurt (Box 30, Folder +)
      - Frankfurt - Goethehaus (Box 30, Folder ++)
      - Garbenheim (Box 31, Folder +)
      - Göttingen (Box 31, Folder +)
      - Gotha (Box 31, Folder +)
      - Halle (Box 31, Folder +)
      - Harz (Box 31, Folder +)
      - Inntal (Box 31, Folder +)
      - Jena (Box 31, Folder +)
      - Johannisberg (Box 31, Folder +)
      - Lahneck (Box 31, Folder +)
      - Leipzig (Box 31, Folder ++)
      - Odilienberg (Box 31, Folder +)
      - Pyrmont (Box 31, Folder +)
      - Rudolstadt (Box 31, Folder +)
      - Rüdesheim (Box 31, Folder +)
      - Taunus (Box 31, Folder +)
      - Thüringen (Box 31, Folder +)
      - Tübingen (Box 31, Folder +)
      - Weimar
        - Complete Views (Box 32, Folder +)
        - Collections of individual views (Box 32, Folder +)
        - Burgplatz (Box 32, Folder +)
        - Karlsplatz (Box 32, Folder +)
        - Churches, Cemetaries, etc. (Box 32, Folder +)
        - Fürstengruft (Box 32, Folder +)
        - Goethes Garten (Box 32, Folder +)
        - Goethes Gartenhaus (Box 32, Folder ++)
        - Goethes Haus (Box 32, Folder +)
        - Goethes Haus - Arbeitszimmer (Box 32, Folder +)
        - Goethes Hausgarten (Box 33, Folder +)
        - Armbrustschiesshaus (Box 33, Folder +)
        - Bibliothek (Box 33, Folder +)
        - Bürgerschule (Box 33, Folder +)
        - Hauptwache (Box 33, Folder +)
        - Freimaurerloge (Box 33, Folder +)
        - Rathaus (Box 33, Folder +)
        - Tempelherrenhaus (Box 33, Folder +)
        - Theater (Box 33, Folder +)
        - Bertuchs Haus & Garten (Box 33, Folder +)
        - Falks Haus (Box 33, Folder +)
        - Herders Haus (Box 33, Folder +)
        - Residenzschloss (Box 33, Folder +)
        - Schillers Haus - Inneres (Box 33, Folder +)
        - Schillers Haus (Box 33, Folder +)
        - Wielands Haus (Box 34, Folder +)
        - Wielands Haus Original by Ed. Lobe (Box 34, Folder +)
        - Wittumspalais (Box 34, Folder ++)
      - Weimar Surroundings
        - Parks, Squares, Monuments (Box 34, Folder ++)
        - Park - Klause (Box 34, Folder +)
        - Park - Läuterbach (Box 34, Folder +)
        - Park - Römisches Haus (Box 34, Folder +)
        - Belvedere (Box 34, Folder +)
        - Ettersburg (Box 34, Folder +)
        - Kromsdorf (Box 34, Folder +)
        - Oberweimar (Box 34, Folder +)
        - Schiesshaus (Box 34, Folder +)
        - Tiefurt (Box 34, Folder ++)
      - Wetzlar (Box 35, Folder ++)
      - Wiesbaden (Box 35, Folder +)
      - Wörlitz (Box 35, Folder +)
      - Unidentified theater, hand drawn from plan (Box 35, Folder +)
    - Italy
      - Miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder +)
      - Bressanone (Box 35, Folder +)
      - Roma (Box 35, Folder +)
      - Vesuvius (Box 35, Folder +)
    - Switzerland
      - Cascade de Pissevache (Box 35, Folder +)
      - Chamouny (Box 35, Folder +)
      - Luzern (Box 35, Folder +)
      - Schaffhausen (Box 35, Folder +)
    - Miscellaneous Views of Italy
      - Seven prints, including one by Piranesi (Box 36, Folder +)
      - Nine prints (Box 37, Folder +)
      - Eight prints, including five by Piranesi (Box 38, Folder +)
      - Twenty prints, one of them by Piranesi (Box 39, Folder +)
      - Three prints, including two by Piranesi (Box 40, Folder +)
      - Four prints, including one by Piranesi (Box 41, Folder +)
  - BOXES: ILLUSTRATIONS
    - Goethe's Works
      - Radirte Blätter (Box 42, Folder +)
      - Erlkönig related material: Gillray "Tales of Wonder!" (colored print) (Box 42, Folder +)
  - DRAWERS: PORTRAITS
    - "A"
      - Arndt, Ernst Moritz, 1769-1860 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Arnim, Bettina Brentano von (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - "B"
      - Basedow, Johann Bernhard, 1723-1790 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Bause, Johann Friedrich, 1738-1814 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Beethoven, Ludwig van (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Blumenbach, Johann Friedrich (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Böhme, Johann Gottlieb, 1717-1780 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Boisserée, Sulpiz, 1783-1854 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Breitkoff, Johann Gottlob Imanuel, 1719-1794 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Byron, George Gordon Noël Byron, 6th baron, 1788-1824 (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - "C"
      - Catalani, Angelica, 1779-1849 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Constant de Rebecque, Henri, 1767-1830 (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - "D"
      - Durand, Friedrich August Aumann, 1787-1852 (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - "E"
      - Eikhof, Hans Konrad Dieterich, 1720-1778 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Ernst August, King of Hanover, 1771-1851 (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - "F"
      - Fiedler, Johann Christian (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Friedrike, Queen of Hanover (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Fries, Jakob Friedrich, 1773-1843 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Fritsch, Karl Wilhelm, Freiherr von (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - "G"
      - Gall, Franz Joseph, 1758-1828 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Garve, Christian, 1742-1798 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Goethe
        - Bauer (Box bsd, Folder +)
        - Dawe - Wright (Box bsd, Folder +)
        - Egloffstein (Box bsd, Folder +)
        - Jagemann (Box bsd, Folder ++)
        - Kiprensky (Box bsd, Folder +)
        - Kolbe (Box bsd, Folder +)
        - Kügelgen (Box bsd, Folder ++)
        - Lips (Box bsd, Folder +)
        - May (Box bsd, Folder ++)
        - Meyer (Box bsd, Folder ++)
        - Preller (Box bsd, Folder +)
        - Raabe (Box bsd, Folder ++)
        - Schmeller (Box bsd, Folder +)
        - Schwerdgeburth (Box bsd, Folder +)
        - Sebbers (Box bsd, Folder +)
        - Seidler (Box bsd, Folder +)
        - Stieler (Box bsd, Folder ++)
        - Tischbien (Box bsd, Folder +)
        - Vogel von Vogelstein (Box bsd, Folder +)
        - Medallions (Box bsd, Folder +)
        - Medals (Box bsd, Folder +)
        - Monuments (Box bsd, Folder +)
        - Miscellaneous (Box bsd, Folder +)
        - Reliefs - Miscellaneous (Box bsd, Folder +)
        - Silhouettes - Miscellaneous (Box bsd, Folder +)
        - Statuettes - Rauch (Box bsd, Folder +)
        - Goethe im Bild
          - Goethe und Friederike (Box bsd, Folder +)
          - Mehr Licht! (Box bsd, Folder +)
        - Group Picture (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Goethe, Frau Katharina Elisabeth Textor, 1731-1808 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Graff, Anton, 1736-1813 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Graff, Johann Jacob, 1768-1848 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Grimm, Wilhelm Karl, 1786-1859 (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - "H"
      - Hackert, Jacob Philipp, 1737-1807 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Hamilton, Emma Lyon, Lady, 1761-1815 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Hegel, Georg Wilhelm Friedrich (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Hemsterhuis, Francisus, 1721-1790 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Herder, Johann Gottfried von, 1744-1803 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Hirt, Aloys Ludwig, 1759-1839 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Holtei, Karl von, 1798-1880 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Hufeland, Christoph Wilhelm, 1762-1836 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Humboldt, Alexander, Freiherr von, 1769-1859 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Hummel, Johann Nepomuk, 1778-1837 (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - "I"
      - Iffland, August Wilhelm, 1759-1814 (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - "J"
      - Jacobi, Friedrich Heinrich, 1743-1819 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Joseph II, emperor of Germany, 1741-1790 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Jung-Stilling, Johann Heinrich, 1740-1817 (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - "K"
      - Karl August, Grand Duke of Saxe-Weimar-Eisenach, 1757-1828 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Karl Friedrich, Grand Duke of Saxe-Weimar-Eisenach, 1783-1853 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Kestner, August, 1777-1853 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Kestner, Frau Charlotte Buff, 1753-1828 (Box bsd, Folder ++)
      - Kestner, Johann Christian, 1741-1800 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Klopstock, Friedrich Gottlieb, 1724-1803 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Konig von Konigsthal, Gustav Georg, Baron, 1717-1771 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Körner, Theodor, 1791-1813 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Kotzebue, August Friedrich Ferdinand von, 1761-1819 (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - "L"
      - La Roche, Frau Sophie von, 1731-1807 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Lavater, Johann Caspar, 1741-1801 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Leopold III, Friedrich Franz, Duke of Anhalt-Dessau, 1740-1817 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Lessing, Gotthold Ephraim, 1739-1781 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Ligne, Charles Joseph, prince de, 1735-1814 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Loen, Johann Michael von (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth, 1807-1882 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Louise Auguste, Grand Duchess of Saxe-Weimar-Eisenach, 1757-1830 (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - "M"
      - Maria Luise Alexandrine, princess of Prussia, 1808-1877 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Mariia Pavlovna, Grand Duchess of Saxe-Weimar-Eisenach, 1786-1859 (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - "N"
      - Niebuhr, Barthold Georg, 1776-1831 (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - "R"
      - Rauch, Christian Daniel, 1777-1857 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Recke, Elisa, Baronin von der, 1754-1833 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Richter, Johann Paul Friedrich, 1763-1825 (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - "S"
      - Savigny, Friedrich Karl von, 1779-1861 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Schadow, Johann Gottfried, 1764-1850 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Schiller, Johann Christoph Friedrich von, 1759-1805 (Box bsd, Folder +++)
      - Schopenhauer, Arthur, 1788-1860 Schopenhauer, Johanna, 1766-1838 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Schroeter, Corona Elisabeth Wilhelmine, 1751-1802 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Senckenberg, Heinrich Christian, Freiherr von, 1704-1768 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Soemmerring, Samuel Thomas von, 1755-1830 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Starck, Johann Christian (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Stein - Family (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Stein, Frau Charlotte Albertine Ernestine von, 1742-1827 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Sternberg, Kaspar, Graf, 1761-1838 (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - "T"
      - Tieck, Johann Ludwig, 1773-1853 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Türckheim, Anna Elisabeth von, 1758-1817 (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - "V"
      - Varnhagen von Ense, Karl August, 1785-1858 (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - "W"
      - Werdy, Friedericke Margarethe (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Wieland, Christoph Martin, 1733-1813 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Willemer, Frau Marianne Jung von, 1784-1860 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Winckelmann, Johann Joachim, 1717-1768 (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Wolf, Friedrich August, 1759-1824 (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - Unidentified
      - Unidentified (Box bsd, Folder +)
  - DRAWERS: VIEWS
    - Austria
      - Igel (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - Czechoslovakia
      - Franzensbad (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Karlsbad (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Marienbad (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - France
      - Strasbourg (Box bsd, Folder ++)
    - Germany
      - Biebrich (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Clausthal (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Dessau (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Dornburg (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Dresden (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Eisenach - Wartburg (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Frankfurt (Box bsd, Folder ++)
      - Frankfurt - Churches & Cemeteries (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Göttingen (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Halberstadt (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Heidelberg (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Halle (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Ilmenau (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Ilmenau - Mine (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Jena (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Lahnstein (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Leipzig (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Mainz (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - München - Statues, etc. (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Sesenheim (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Weimar
        - Miscellaneous views (Box bsd, Folder ++)
        - Park (Box bsd, Folder +)
        - Goethestätten (Box bsd, Folder +)
        - Celebrations (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Wernigerode (Box bsd, Folder +)
      - Wörlitz (Box bsd, Folder +)
    - Italy